Context engineering is the new big thing
for AI coding. Not because it's brand
new, but because people are finally
acknowledging that putting the time up
front to provide extensive context to AI
coding assistance is what separates real
results from vibe coding and basic
prompt engineering. And most people are
still experimenting with these ideas
without a true systematic process. And
so in this video, I want to dive into
using context engineering for real
production builds. essentially taking my
template that I covered on my channel
recently, but going much deeper for you.
Now, here's why context engineering is
such a big deal. We know that vibe
coding builds prototypes that break when
you try to scale. And prompt engineering
is all about word tweaking. Working with
specific phrases to get single better
outputs from LLMs. In fact, the way I've
heard it recently is context engineering
is a supererset of prompt engineering.
It's a part of it, but context
engineering is so much more. It's
providing all information, examples,
best practices, constraints to AI coding
assistants upfront. It certainly is a
time investment, but man will it 10x
your process for building literally
anything. And I mean that. Now, there
are many ways to go about context
engineering. But the strategy that I
keep coming back to time and time again
that my template for you is also based
on is the PRP framework from Raasmus.
And this is just genius. And Raasmus is
actually a guest for a part of this
video today. So I'm really excited for
you to see that. He's going to dive into
PRP, his philosophy behind it, why it
works so well, how you can get started
with it right now. And then what we've
done together is we have actually taken
my base template that I have in the
context engineering repo and we've made
one that's specific to building MCP
servers. So you can use the PRP
framework to build any production ready
MCP server that you want just as a super
practical use case. And we're actually
going to go through and build one
together in this video using this exact
blueprint. So let me show you what I
mean. If we go back to the root of the
context engineering repo, which this is
the template that I'll have linked for
you in the description of the video, by
the way, everything that we have here is
a generic template for using the PRP
framework. Like if we go into our slash
commands here, these are just very
generic slash commands that would work
no matter the application that you want
to build. And then if we go back out and
we look at our PRPS, we have the
template here. Again, just very, very
generic. This applies to any kind of
software, but there's certainly an
opportunity to make a template for you
that's already crafted to be much more
specific to a certain kind of use case.
And that's exactly what Raasmus and I
have been working on for you. So, we
actually took the productionready
Cloudflare MCP server I showed in the
last video on my channel and we built a
template around it. So, we're going back
here to the use cases MCP server folder
in my template. We've taken the MCP
server that I built my last video as an
example built into this template and if
we look at the slash commands for
example, we've made things much more
specific to building MCP servers. And
even more importantly, we did the same
thing with the base PRP. This is the
reference that we use to create that
full PRP. And now everything is very
specific to building MCP servers. And so
now you can use this as a launching pad
no matter the MCP server that you want
to create. And you're going to get much
better results because things are so
hyper tuned to building an MCP server.
And by the way, going through this
process yourself to build an MCP could
not be easier. And this is what I'm
going to show you how to do after we
have our chat with Raasmus. So literally
you just have to go into this
initial.mmd file which I talked about
initial.md in my first video on context
engineering. You fill out the
information for the MCP that you want to
create and then you generate your PRP
with this slash command which can just
be a prompt for any other AI coding
assistant besides cloud code. And then
it's important to validate the PRP and
be a part of this process. Don't trust
the AI blindly. But then you can execute
your PRP and this is going to build your
MCP server and you can just iterate from
there. It is that easy to get started
and a lot of this is revolving around
the power of this MCP PRPbased template
that we've crafted for you. And this my
friend is just the beginning. Actually a
huge project that I'm starting in the
Dynamis community is essentially
building out a massive repository of all
of these use cases. So no matter the
programming language that we're using or
the type of application that we're
building, there's going to be a template
here using the PRP framework, but much
more hyper tuned to what we want to
build. And that's exactly what I'm
showing you here with MCP just as a
super good example. And by the way, if
you're interested in this and just
taking your AI coding to the next level
in general, definitely check out
Dynamus.ai. There's so many things
happening there like building out all of
these PRP templates. So, I'm about to
show you a live example of the MCP
server that we built based on this
template, and we did it in two shots.
There was one follow-up prompt that we
had to do to fix two bugs. But after
that, we have 18 perfectly working tools
in this very non-trivial MCP server.
It's so cool. This is the PRP taskmaster
MCP. You give a PRP and it'll extract
tasks based on that and help you manage
them. It is very similar to Claude
Taskmaster but for PRPS instead of PRDS.
Now it's not the most practical MCP
server though I will probably be
building it into Archon at some point.
So stay tuned for that for Archon
version two. But I wanted to give a nod
to Claude Taskmaster because it really
is an incredible MCP for context
engineering. And I thought this would be
a good example showing how we can
replicate something that's already out
in the wild that is really incredible
and like I said not trivial. And so I've
got a prompt pre-crafted here. And this
is what I love doing when I'm testing an
MCP server for the first time. I just
say, "We've got this new MCP." I tell it
what it's responsible for doing. And
then I just say, "I want you to test all
the functionality of this server with a
flow that actually makes sense for
starting a new project, adding tasks and
dependencies, documentation. We have the
tools to manage all of these different
things. And I'm just saying don't go
overboard. We just want a simple
demonstration here." and then create a
sample PRP just to start things off. So,
I'm just using mock data here and I've
got my database already set up. So, we
have our projects table, tasks, task
dependencies. There's quite a bit that's
going on behind the scenes to manage
everything with this MCP. And so, yeah,
let's just go ahead and kick things off
here. And so, it's going to start by
mocking a PRP, sending that in to
extract the tasks from it. And so, I'm
going to pause and come back once it has
done this because this part takes a
little bit. is actually using the
anthropic API under the hood here. And
there we go. Our project is created. We
can actually verify this. So, if I go to
the projects, yep, we got a simple to-do
app that we've have added to our
database. And now it wants to list
projects. So, we'll go ahead and let it
do that. And then we're going to also
have the tasks already in here. So, if I
go into my tasks, we can see that we
have a few already. And so, now it'll
just go through list the tasks and just
kind of go through a mock flow, I
assume, of marking some tasks off. Yep.
So getting the project overview is
probably going to add some documentation
as well. But yeah, you can see how it
it's just knocking out one tool at a
time, testing everything for me so that
I just know that my MCP server is
working correctly. And especially when
you are using something like the PRP
framework and you're coding something
with the help of AI pretty heavily, it
is important to validate everything like
you do want to test every single tool in
your MCP server for example. And that's
a big thing that we'll see in our
conversation with Raasmus is validation
is still super important. Like when you
generate your PRP, you still want to
make sure that you're analyzing it,
being a part of the process, not just
generating the PRP and then executing
it, right? And it's the same thing with
the output as well. Like you want to
understand the code that it outputed.
Validate that test things like I'm doing
right here and have the AI coding
assistant create tests as well. And so
yeah, I think that's enough of the
testing here. Everything is looking
really, really good. I don't want to
bore you with the rest of this demo, but
yeah, that is our MCP server at a high
level. And like I said, we could use
this template to build literally any MCP
server, and it's going to be production
ready. And there we go. We have all of
the core functionality tested for our
MCP server. Things are looking really
good. So, here's what's coming up next
for you. First, a quick word from our
sponsor. Then, we'll dive into the
conversation with Raasmus. And man, that
is one that you don't want to miss. It
was a pleasure having him on the
channel. And then last but not least,
I'll show you my full replicable process
for building this MCP server with the
PRP template that I showed you already.
This, my friend, is Peak AI coding. The
sponsor of today's video is Lindy. Think
of it like if AI and Zapier had a baby,
but what really makes their platform
stand out to me is their feature for
parallel agents called agent swarms.
Take a look at this. So you build your
workflows just like you would with
something like N8N, but you can create
these loops here where it's going to
spin up many different agents to knock
out a bunch of tasks for you at the
exact same time. So this workflow
specifically is for deep research. And
so I can have many agents spun up at the
same time. You could change this to the
top 10, the top 20. So to research all
these subtopics at the exact same time.
So it's much faster than something like
OpenAI's deep research. And so just to
go along with the theme of our video
here, I'll ask what are the best
strategies for using claude code. And
we'll see in a second once it enters the
loop, it's going to create multiple
different agents all at the same time
spun up to research different angles for
my question. And so it'll still take
some time because it does pretty deep
research here. And so we'll see in a
little bit all the loops will complete
and then it'll give us our final
response. And there we go. All the loops
have completed. It's done. the deep
research for each of my different
angles. And then in a second here, we'll
see the final summary spit out. So, this
is the research that was done for each
of these agents. And there we go. We now
have our full deep research. Also, Lindy
has partnered with Pipeream to give you
more than 5,000 integrations across 25
different apps and 4,000 web scrapers
through their partnership with Appify.
There is not a platform with more
integrations than Lindy. So, I'll have a
link in the description to Lindy. You'll
also get 400 credits for free to try out
the platform when you use that link. So
definitely go ahead and check them out.
All right, we have the man himself here,
Raasmus, the creator of the PRP
framework, and I'm just really excited
to bring you in, talk about the
framework, your vision for it, your
philosophy behind it, because there are
a million ways to context engineer. It's
a pretty new phrase overall, but it's
not a new idea, right? Um, but the PRP
framework is just what I've been going
to time and time again recently. And
it's just made my AI coding that much
better, like 10 times, hundred times
better. And so I just absolutely love
it. And I know that you've been
developing out this framework for over a
year now, which is insanely impressive.
And so I just wanted to hear from you
what inspired this and where you're
going with it. So yeah, if you want to
feel free and just introduce yourself,
kick things off um telling us about the
PRP framework. Uh, by the way guys, we
met in the Dynamis community and when he
was first sharing this PRP framework, it
just stuck out to me immediately. Like I
knew it wasn't just another one of the
thousand strategies I'd heard like this
is the real deal. So yeah, let's hear
from you Raasmus.
>> Yeah, thanks for that intro. So yeah,
um, first of all, uh, since you also
featured the PRP framework in your
context engineering video, just want to
say thanks to everyone who has embraced
it and sent me all of the amazing
projects that you have built on top of
it. uh I've seen some really awesome
stuff there. Uh but yeah, so what uh PRP
is, it's a product requirement prompt.
I've spent many years as a product
manager and business analyst writing a
lot of technical documentation and PRDS
in particular. So PRP is really my
attempt at building a prompt framework
around uh product management. So like
bringing the context needed uh for a
coding agent to build the feature or the
product that I wanted to build. So
that's uh uh the basic idea.
Uh in in short I would like to just
describe it here. So it's uh a PRP is a
PRD plus curated codebase intelligence
plus agent runbook and it's aiming to be
the minimum viable packet an AI needs to
plausibly ship production ready code uh
on the first pass. So as you as you said
as well I've been developing this for
kind of over a year. It has had in that
year it has many many shapes and forms
uh and it started out using like aer and
clin as the main drivers and uh yeah
it's very inspired by in the devdan and
the client community and the memory
prompting uh framework uh that that a
lot of people use over there
but yeah that's how we got started. uh I
needed it for a for an existing project
that I was building at the time,
valuation engine. So yeah, I I used PRP
or the very baby version of PRP to to
build that out and and ship it to
production. So
>> yeah, that's really cool. Thanks for
sharing, Rasmus. And the thing that
sticks out in this read me here is the
industry mantra, garbage in, garbage out
applies doubly to prompt engineering.
And that is so true. And that also
speaks to the fact that like prompt
engineering very much is a part of
context engineering and the PRP
framework, but really those are a
superset. There's so much more that goes
into how we're engineering the context
here, especially with the PRP framework
and how far we can take things with it.
And so speaking of that, actually, let's
uh hop over to the template now in
GitHub. Specifically, what we wanted to
give you guys with this template is just
a clear example of how you can apply the
PRP framework to build something new.
And so, this is very much based off of
my last video on context engineering
where I gave more of an intro, but now
we're showing you a real example with a
template that you can use literally to
take this use a PRP framework to build
any MCP server that you want. So it's
also based on my last video where I
showed building production ready MCP
servers with Cloudflare and TypeScript,
but now we've put everything related to
PRP on top of it so that you can go
through and build your own MCP. So
Razis, I'll I'll just let you do the
explaining for how this works and how
people can get started with this. You're
definitely going to do that better than
me.
>> Yeah. So that's exactly what you just
described is what we did, right? So, we
took what you did in your past two
videos, context engineering uh with the
PRP framework and also the MCP server uh
starter template that you built and we
put together specialized PRP prompts and
templates that will help you build any
MCP server you can build. And I can
pretty confidently say that this is
probably the easiest way to build an MCP
server. So uh what you really need to do
is you take your plan uh whatever you
want to build and you define it in
initial.mmd.
So this can be uh
try to describe it like as good as you
can like all your tools you want to have
your business logic in as much detail as
you can. Uh and then you will uh take
that plan and then you will run that
through the PRP framework. So you can
use LLMs to start planning your your
work and everything. So I highly
encourage you to use LLMs also in your
planning and preparation.
Uh then you will run the first slash
command which is the PRB uh base create
or MCP create and you will pass your
plan as the argument. And what this
really does is this is what uh this is
where the context gathering part
happens. So it will pull in all of the
context that it thinks it's that it
needs to to finish your work like all
the uh context that the AI itself thinks
that it will need to to complete the
work uh of your plan and it will pull it
into this base template. If we take a
quick look at this base template though,
we have already done a lot of that
context engineering uh for you. So a lot
of the references that the AI will need
is already in here. So it will only
build on top of what we have already
created for you here. So this uh base
template already has a lot of references
to uh the template that Cole built uh
last week. So it references all of the
patterns, it references the tool, the
tool registry, how to do that, the
database and and yeah, it really
references a lot of things here that
comes from that template. Uh so uh when
you run the first command, it will pull
your idea and add more context really to
this uh template as needed.
>> The beauty of that is we have this
template already made for you. So
there's a lot of context engineering
that goes into the PRP framework, but
there's just a lot less when you have
this as a starting point. And that's
actually something that Raasmus and I
want to start up really soon here is
working on a repository of all of these
base PRP templates. So no matter the
programming language you're using or the
specific type of project like an MCP
server you want to make, there's going
to be some template to give you this
massive launching pad. So you can create
all of this context but not have to do
it all from scratch. Like you have this
starting point and then also there's a
lot of like manual work that goes into
really making these PRPs robust as well.
And I know that you wanted to touch on
that too, Raasmus.
>> Yeah, I mean you can just take the
example that that me and Cole has built
here like we spent a lot of time like
manually or semianually I would say
because we took a lot of help from cloud
code of course to prepare the context
for this base template. So uh whenever
you have created your um like your base
template, you always should read through
it and make sure that it actually
references the things that you uh want
and that you need it to reference so
that it doesn't say something weird. So
a lot of time I spend a lot of time
actually like reading through these and
making sure that they are good before I
execute them because especially when I
execute things in parallel I need to
make sure that they are not uh tangled
too much. So even if I run them in
different workies I don't want to have
the conflicts when I try to merge it
later on. So if if you want to scale
this up especially, you need to make
sure that they're not tangled, but you
also need to make sure that they are
actually following the business logic
that you intend them to follow.
>> So read through your your PRPs before
you run the execute command, which is
the last step.
>> Yeah, definitely. Yeah, validation is
always important and that's the big
thing that like is so wrong with vibe
coding, right? Is there just never that
validation and we need that even for the
context that we're engineering. And I
think like the the last big piece that
we haven't hit on here is our claw.md or
just whatever your global rules are for
your AI coding assistant, which by the
way, you can use this whole process with
the Gemini CLI or cursor or windsurf.
You don't have the idea of slash
commands like you do in cloud code, but
you can just take these slash commands
and then use them as regular prompts,
right? And so, yeah, diving into global
rules now. Uh, I want to dive into this
with you, Raasmus, because I think a
really big distinction we need to make
here is when do you put context in the
global rules like cloud.mmd versus when
does it belong in the PRP?
>> Yeah. So, uh I I like to think of it
like this like I I treat my cloud MD as
where I put like the constant rules that
will very rarely change. So things that
will be true forever in my codebase and
things that will be added to my codebase
that also will be true forever or for a
very long time.
>> So uh whenever you add like a new
principle like a new naming standard or
maybe a new uh function that is really
really core to your codebase also you
can add it there. Uh so so yeah things
that will stay the same for a long time.
Uh but also append new things that keep
coming in. You can also put cloud MD
files in specific folders that
references specific things in that
module or folder. That's also really
powerful. Then I like to think of the
slash commands as really where they
should just be like dropins uh for for
whatever uh thing you're working on. So
they shouldn't hold any specific. So the
create command is just a planning it's
just like a huge planning workflow
really. what like a research workflow
that has really nothing to do with
anything specific.
>> It becomes specific because you pass in
your specific plan. And the same goes
with execute. Execute command is just a
ch prompt chain or um a prompt that will
tell the AI how to execute your PRP. So
it has nothing to do with the PRP
itself. And then the base PRP is really
where you put your specific context to
that specific piece of work that you're
doing right now.
>> Yeah, that's really good. And I just
like the phrasing there like cloud.mmd
is where the things go that aren't going
to change because really when you start
to work on existing codebase, you'll
have kind of a mini PRP for each feature
that you want to develop because there's
always going to be slightly different
ways that you want it to go about
implementing a feature. But claw.md
that's the things that are the same
between all of those features. And
actually that kind of leads to the next
question that I wanted to ask you
Raasmus is how well does the PRP
framework work on existing code bases? I
know it's something that people have
been asking quite a bit.
>> Yeah, I mean I think uh it's purposely
built for working on existing code
bases. So that's the use case I needed
it for when I started building it. It
definitely wasn't perfect when I started
building it, but I bet I made a quite
big bet that it would soon work well
with with better model and I think
especially with cloud code, we have seen
that happened. So like even the
difference between how it worked with
cloud 3.7 and cloud 4 is is like insane.
Like I used to kick off like a 100 line
PRP and and it would run it like
reliably nine times out of 10 maybe
seven times out of 10 and after cloud 4
I can kick off like a 500 line prompt
reliably a thousand line prompt
semi-reliably and I have have kicked off
1500 line prompts reliably you know not
not 10 out of 10 of course but you know
like experimentally I I try try a lot of
things.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, and it's important to
say like it ain't perfect. It definitely
isn't, but it it feels close. Like it's
just incredible the kind of things that
we can build with the PRP framework and
just using that as our way to context
engineer. And uh the last question that
I want to ask you, Raasmus, actually the
one that I've gotten the most ever since
I made my context engineering intro
video, is why put this much time into
context engineering? I know that we've
talked about this throughout our
conversation, but I definitely sense
there going to be some people that are
still hesitant to put this much time
into sharpening their axe, so to speak.
So, what would you have to say to that?
Like, why should we put the time into
engineering this much context?
>> Yeah. So, for me, it's obvious because I
come from product management. So, I used
to do this anyways. So I used to do this
type of work anyways but not for an AI
assistant but for a team of developers.
So it's really just builds on that like
someone building a real project someone
is doing this work whether it's you or
whether it's an AI or someone else.
>> So really thinking deep about the the
important questions like why are we
building this in the first place? Who
are we building it for? How exactly
should the user experience look like?
Those are really important question
questions to answer and then making the
decisions of how to build that
like when you build your first prototype
of something or or a version of
something you have to like make that
decision
>> and then go test it on users and when
you work on a real existing codebase you
will get a lot of that feedback from
users already. So you can like build
your PRP based on the user feedback that
you're getting already. So that's that's
why it works so well on existing things
too. not only that you get already have
user feedback to get but you also have
an existing codebase to follow. That's
exactly what this example is showing as
well that when we have like like this
could have been possible to to oneshot
this like large piece of work without
having such a good foundation that this
MCP server template really has. So the
AI will have like all of these patterns
to follow that already exists uh that
will help us build this out uh reliably.
Yeah, that is really good. Thank you,
Raasmus. That's everything that I had
for questions here and you just set the
stage so well for why we should care
about PRP and how it works too. And so
now what I want to walk everyone through
is a a live example using this template
to build an MCP server from scratch. And
so I'll show you everything that Rasmus
walked us through, but we're going to go
through it step by step. So I'll create
that initial MD, right? I'll generate
the PRP. We'll build the MCP server and
validate everything. And it's just
amazing the results we get. So thank you
Raasmus for walking us through
everything. And now let's get into the
demo. So here we are in the readme for
the MCP server template that I have in
the context engineering intro
repository. This is what I was showing
earlier in GitHub. And so now I have it
cloned locally. I'll walk you through
the three steps here to create our MCP
server from scratch with all the context
that we have as a launching point. And
so we'll create the initial MD where we
describe the MCP server that we want. We
will generate and validate our PRP and
then finally execute it and then you can
iterate from there and deploy to
Cloudflare workers. And definitely check
out my last video on this MCP server
that I have as a starting point for you
if you want to go into the whole deploy
to Cloudflare side of things. And
speaking of that MCP server that is a
part of the context here. So we're
essentially taking that MCP server
turning it into a scaffold that we have
in this template. So we have everything
around PRP plus the MCP server as a
scaffold. And then all we need to do
with our PRP when we generate and
execute it is essentially tell it how to
take the skeleton of an MCP server and
add all of our custom tools. That's what
we're going to be doing here. And so we
need to start by editing our initial MD.
So that's within the PRP's folder. And
then within here we can describe the MCP
server that we want to create based on
this template. And so I have an example
kind of fully written out here. This is
to build our PRP taskmaster MCP that I
demoed earlier, but you can adjust this
to whatever you want to build. I just
generally recommend keeping the feature
section. Then we have the examples and
documentation, which a lot of that we
already have set up in this MCP specific
PRP base that we've been talking about.
And then other considerations is also
very important. This is a good place to
reference any gotchas that AI coding
assistants seem to mess up on a lot.
like I talk about uh how to use
environment variables for example and
this is very much following the initial
MD that I described setting up in my
last video on context engineering. So
it's very much the case that we took the
root of this repository and now we've
just made a super specific version to
building MCP servers with my last MCP as
added context kind of like a scaffold
right so that's the beauty of this and
so what I've done in my initial MD is
I've said something pretty simple here
like we want to build an MCP we want to
create a simple version of the
taskmaster but parsing u PRPs instead of
PRDs and I probably could have been a
lot more specific here but I just wanted
to show this as a demo. And so your
initial MD might be quite a bit longer.
You might want to be a lot more
specific. This is just to get you
started. It's just to give you a general
idea of what would go in each section.
So the these are all the features that
we want in our MCP, like the different
tools we're looking for. And like Raasma
said, you might want to actually have a
PRP per tool if you really want to make
sure it nails it. In our case, this is
actually working really well, which is
just insane. And then for the example
documentation, most of it is already
within our PRP MCP base. And then also
I'm giving it the GitHub repository to
Claude Taskmaster. So as a part of our
PRP, we are going to tell Claude code to
actually go look at the implementation
so it understands all the tools there so
it can replicate that for our PRP
taskmaster MCP. And then just a few
considerations that I've got here at the
bottom. So that is my initial MD. And
then going back to the readme here, let
me open up the readme. Once you have
that set up, now we just need to
generate our PRP. So I'm going to do
Ctrl J to open up a terminal here in my
VS code. And then I'll type in Claude.
So we are within Claude. And then I will
do slash. And then all we have to do is
slash PRP MCPre. I can press tab to
autocomplete. And then I just have to
specify my initial MD which you can just
call out the file name itself or even
better the relative path to the file in
the repository like this. Boom. There we
go. So I'll go ahead and send this in.
I'll do shift tab so that autoedit is
on. And now it's going to do a bunch of
research based on the MCP that I want to
create based on the PRP MCP base. And
it's going to create a custom PRP for me
based on this template. And it's going
to take a while. It does quite a bit of
research and architecting and planning.
And so I'll pause and come back once we
have our PRP and then we'll validate it
together. And there we go. After about
10 to 15 minutes, we have our custom PRP
generated. So I'll do Ctrl J to exile to
my terminal. Click into this PRP and
let's take a look. And so remember, we
need to validate everything here. And
these are pretty long. Generally, these
PRPs can get quite lengthy, but it is
worth taking a look at everything, at
least glazing over the details here,
making sure there's nothing crazy,
making sure that it's actually going to
implement the MCP server or the
application that you want to implement.
And so yeah, let's take it from the top
here. So we are building an MCP server.
The goal is to build a productionready
MCP for a PRP parsing system. Task
management tools. We got GitHub OOTH,
Cloudflow worker deployments. We're
using Postgress to manage everything in
our database. This is looking really
good. And it lists out the tools that we
want for PRP parsing, task management,
documentation, basically everything that
you saw in the demo earlier. Really,
really good authentication, database.
And one thing I want to show you that's
really important is we always want to
have a section in the PRP that talks
about all the documentation and
references that we want to bring into
the context for our AI coding assistant
when we execute the PRP. And so this is
something that you definitely want to
reveal in detail because everything that
we have listed here it's going to be
reading through and using as its
reference point for implementation. So
it'll understand here how to register
new tools for our MCP and hook that into
our scaffolding. That's super important.
It's going to analyze the existing
codebase to see how we set up our MCP
server. We've got official documentation
from MCP. So, generally, you want to
have a good mix between external sources
like our official MCP docs and then our
existing codebase and examples that
we're giving and all that together
holistically creates all of the context
along with the PRP. There's just so much
that goes into this. The other thing
that's really cool is generally with
PRPs, what Rasmus and I have been doing
is having it list out the current
structure for the codebase and then the
desired structure, what we want to add
or modify for the final MCP server
implementation. And man, this just gives
so much structure. And I've seen Cloud
Code especially just stick with this so
well. Like every time I use this kind of
PRP, whatever it outputs, like it
actually matches this structure like
file by file. It's so so cool. And so
there's not a lot that I've actually
wanted to change at this point. Uh so if
we keep scrolling down, one thing that I
did notice off camerara here is that it
wants to update thedev.vars,
which that's kind of Cloudflare's
equivalent of aenv. You don't typically
want your AI coding assistants to
actually go and edit your secrets
directly. So I would want to take this
section out. And so that's just to give
you an example of something that like
you very much would want to change. And
that's why it's so important to validate
your PRPS. I don't want to bore you with
the details of like tweaking everything
right here. And so my plan right now is
to go through this entire PRP myself
like I'd recommend you doing. I'll
adjust things as I see fit. Then I'll
come back and we will execute this PRP.
All right. So I've made some adjustments
to the PRP. Really making sure that it's
implementing what I want it to do based
on my initial MD. There's not a ton that
I had to change overall. Like it did a
really good job. And so now we can move
on to the last part of the process where
we execute our PRP. And yeah, this is
really simple overall, especially
because of how we can use this template
as such a good starting point for
building MCPS. And that's what I want to
continue to build out for a lot of other
use cases you would care about making as
well. And so what I would generally
recommend doing once you go back into
Claude here is I'd recommend exiting or
clearing the conversation. Typically,
you want to clear the context. So,
you're starting with a blank slate when
you move on to executing the PRP. And
so, now it's going to be PRP MCP
execute. Again, just tab to
autocomplete. And then what we want to
do is just pass in the relative path to
our new PRP. So, it's PRP and then PRP
parsermc.md.
There we go. All right. And I got auto
accept edits on. Now, it's going to
first analyze a PRP, and then it's going
to go through all of the documentation
and example files and everything, create
a comprehensive to-do list, and then
it's going to start knocking out the
tasks one by one. And it's even going to
implement what Raasmus likes to call
validation gates. So, it's going to have
linting, and it'll create unit tests,
and it'll run those unit tests and
iterate on that until the MCP server is
complete and working from at least what
it can tell, right? And so, it's a
pretty extensive process. like this is
going to go on for a while. And so you
can go and, you know, take your dog on a
walk, go and work on another project,
come back once this is done, and you're
going to have an insane starting point
for an MCP. It doesn't always oneot, but
sometimes it can as well. And so, yeah,
I will pause and come back once we have
our implementation. And there we go.
After about 25 minutes, Cloud Code
knocked out all of the tasks for us, and
we now have our fully implemented MCP
server. Take a look at all of the tools
that I built here. And we have green
check marks across the board. And so now
we can use Wrangler, the Cloudflare CLI
to run our MCP. And I'm not going to
dive into the details for how that all
works with Wrangler and Cloudflare. You
can definitely check out my last video
where I really build out this MCP with
you to get those kind of details. But
right here, we can use the Wrangler dev
command to run it. Specifying the
configuration that Cloud Code just made
for our new MCP server, our PRP task
master. So there we go. or run this.
It'll simulate my production CloudFlare
environment. So I basically have a local
worker running and this is my URL to
access the MCP server either with
streamable HTTP or SSE for legacy
purposes. And so going back into my IDE
here within my cloud desktop
configuration, I've added this for my
PRP taskmaster. So just pointing to that
URL and then /mcp for streamable HTTP
and then I can restart my cloud desktop.
So, let me do that really quickly. Bring
it over here. All right. And there we
go. And then if you want to check and
make sure that your MCP server is
connected properly, you just click on
search and tools. Go down and there we
go. We have our PRP task master with the
18 tools that we have implemented. This
is just so so cool. All right. And so I
will say that off camera I had to
iterate one time to get things working.
There's just a couple of bugs and I
think there's like one tool that I
needed to tweak, but otherwise it worked
really well. So it was a twoshot for
this MCP server and it is basically the
same as my last demo. So I'll just use
the same prompt here so we can kick this
off and just kind of see it in action
here like we did earlier. But yeah, we
are good to go. And so now you could
take this and deploy it to Cloudflare.
You can follow the instructions in the
read and also in the repo specifically
for my Cloudflare worker remote MCP
which I'll have that linked in the
description as well. But yeah, the main
thing that I wanted to show you here is
done. We went through the three-step
process creating an MCP server using
context engineering specifically with
the PRP framework. It is just fantastic.
And so yeah, we can see this in action
here. It's going to yep validate our PRP
and ask us to approve this action which
I'll go ahead and do. I won't show the
full demo again, but yeah, things are
looking really good. So we have built an
MCP server from scratch. You can go
through the same process no matter the
MCP that you want to make. So there you
have it. That is everything that I
wanted to show you for context
engineering and specifically doing it
with the PRP framework. So I hope you
can use this as a starting point to very
easily build any MCP server that you
want. And with a bit of imagination, you
can see how you could adjust this to
make anything that you want. That's the
beauty of context engineering is it's
going to 10x your workflow no matter
what you want to make. And like I said,
me and the Dynamus community, we want to
build out this repository of all these
different templates to help you get
started with anything. And that is the
future of AI coding. So if you
appreciated this video and you're
looking forward to more things AI coding
and AI agents, I'd really appreciate a
like and a subscribe. And with that, I
will see you in the next